# **Anil Nakum**

Surat, Gujarat, India



anilnakum213@gmail.com



9904365884



linkedin.com/in/anil-nakum-330413118

# Summary

Experienced MEAN StackDeveloper & PHP Developer with over 5+years of experience in Software development. Excellent reputation for resolving problems, improving customer satisfaction, and driving overall operational improvements. Skilled in Angular, NodeJs, Codeigniter, SQL, JS, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) and HTML. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Engineering from G.K. BHARAD INSTITUTE OF ENGG., KASTURBA DHAM, RAJKOT 059.

### **Experience**



## mt Senior Software Engineer

ManekTech

Nov 2022 - Present (7 months)

# Senior Web Developer

Sarvadhi Solutions Pvt. Ltd. Jun 2021 - Nov 2022 (1 year 6 months)

# B Web Developer

**IBL INFOTECH** Sep 2019 - Jun 2021 (1 year 10 months)

# PHP Developer

OneSourceWebs Oct 2017 - Aug 2019 (1 year 11 months) Working on Codigniter PHP Framework

# PHP Developer

E2logy

May 2017 - Sep 2017 (5 months) Work On PHP Yii2 MVC Framework

#### Education



#### 🧊 G.K. BHARAD INSTITUTE OF ENGG., KASTURBA DHAM, RAJKOT 059

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering 2013 - 2017

#### Skills

TypeScript • HTML5 • PhpMyAdmin • Front-End Development • Node.js • Angular • JavaScript • AJAX • Codigniter • Web Development